{
    "id": "7fe66202f5f2472ab4519be2ceef5c0c",
    "title": "Many And Many Of",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "……………… families own cars these days.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Many",
                "Many of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fadb6fc9f09a4374ae6576080e7d7fd7"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. us were disappointed.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Many",
                "Many of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f0c7f48ee0f74ebdb769a2cf46935590"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. them were late.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Many",
                "Many of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "057f58afc51946ffb1f7bbf93654385c"
        },
        {
            "question": "There were ……………….. children among the audience.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "many of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7d6f0e25bfe140c1a2cab2e7edf8c942"
        },
        {
            "question": "How …………………. you can solve this?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "many of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "170bdfec46ae42af8fe7db367bd5e195"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have thought about him …………………. times.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "many of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b6d03927cd5c400188470acfbf691916"
        },
        {
            "question": "Yes, ……………….. us are interested in the proposal.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "many of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cbaee4ddf93c4039a1c6764b3b069375"
        },
        {
            "question": "There were ……………… people who didn’t like the idea.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "many of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8007a412ea3141f2850b3777eec71c0c"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have told you this ………………. times.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "many of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2966ab9578e147a193e7c3f8e9749839"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have seen her ……………….. times.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "many of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "731738be091b48f599391adfb2567592"
        }
    ]
}